Finding Aid for University of Michigan News and Information Services Photographs, 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series E (Photographic Prints, Slides, Negatives)
  - Slides
    - Moore, Jeff, Cicada Images
      - 1991-1995 (Box E24)
    - Morris, Michael 1995 (Box E24)
    - North Campus and Detroit 1992 (Box E24)
    - Physics Spark Chamber (Box E24)
    - Putnam, Dave, Chemical Engineering, Fluidized Bed Research 1995 (Box E24)
    - Robertson, Sandy, Sticky Protons 1995 (Box E24)
    - Rock 5 (Box E24)
    - Sam Wu Lab 1995 (Box E24)
    - Solar Vision 1995 (Box E24)
    - Survival Flight Images (Box E24)
    - Van der Plujim/Pares, Spain (Box E24)
    - Walker and Pertin, Laser Images 1994 (Box E24)
    - Wise, Ken. College of Engineering (Box E24)
    - Women in Science-Equity Agenda (Box E24)
- Series F circa 1955-1965, 35 millimeter film containers (strip negatives)
  SERIES F (4 linear ft.; ca. 1955-1965) is made up of film canisters filled with rolls of black and white 35mm negatives beginning about 1955 and running through the early 1960s. Broad ranges of subjects are documented, such as campus scenes, athletics, buildings, student activities, and events. The canisters are numbered and listed her in number order.
  - University Hospital, Women's Hospital, Maternity [2] (Box F1)
  - Engineering [3] (Box F1)
  - Flint College [4a] (Box F1)
  - University Hospital, Hospital School, Playroom [4b-5] (Box F1)
  - University Hospital, Angiographic Unit, Heart Catheterization [6] (Box F1)
  - May Festival 1959 [7] (Box F1)
  - Biological Station July 1959 [8a-e] (Box F1)
  - Great Lakes September 1959 [9a-b] (Box F1)
  - Girls' State, Brucker, Hard, etc. September 1959 [10] (Box F1)
  - Iranian Ambassador [11] (Box F1)
  - Outstanding Achievement Awards, Glee Club 1958 [13] (Box F1)
  - Dean Doerr's Film September 1959 [14] (Box F1)
  - Stirzaker [15] (Box F1)
  - Twins [16] (Box F1)
  - Iranian Scholar Carasteh (?) [17] (Box F1)
  - Boy in Fountain [18] (Box F1)
  - Chemistry, Testing Acids [19] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix Building, Iron Age Request [20] (Box F1)
  - Astronomy, Interview (?) Aznar (?) [21] (Box F1)
  - Scholar-Ator, Bill West [22] (Box F1)
  - Miss Tojo [23] (Box F1)
  - Festival of Song [24] (Box F1)
  - Language Lab [25] (Box F1)
  - Michifish (Synchronized Swimming) [26 a-b] (Box F1)
  - Hospital [27 a] (Box F1)
  - Russian Educators [27b] (Box F1)
  - Pickle Barrel Reactor [28] (Box F1)
  - Law School, Phoenix, Hospital March 1959 [29] (Box F1)
  - Marching Band, Hometowns [30-31] (Box F1)
  - Marching Band, Michigan State [32 a] (Box F1)
  - Return to ? (entertainment) [32 b] (Box F1)
  - Marching Band, Oregon State [33] (Box F1)
  - Radio Telescope Dedication [34] (Box F1)
  - Flint College [35] (Box F1)
  - Football, Wisconsin [36] (Box F1)
  - Public Health [37] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix Theratron [38] (Box F1)
  - Law School [39] (Box F1)
  - Outstanding Achievement Awards November 21, 1959 [40] (Box F1)
  - Michi-Reno-Bender [41 a] (Box F1)
  - Hospital, Typewriter [41 b] (Box F1)
  - Heart Pump [42 a] (Box F1)
  - Business Administration, Paul McCracken [42 b] (Box F1)
  - James Brunk [43] (Box F1)
  - Kresge Medical Library [45] (Box F1)
  - Pharmacology [46] (Box F1)
  - Alumnus Supermarket [47] (Box F1)
  - Phi Chi, Medical Fraternity [48] (Box F1)
  - Alumnus Laundromat, Special Publicity, Piano Department [49] (Box F1)
  - Jennifer and Tod Vosu [50] (Box F1)
  - Lander, Mailroom, Yemagiva [51] (Box F1)
  - Willow Run Airport [52] (Box F1)
  - Hospital, Dr. James Conway [54] (Box F1)
  - Civil Defense and Disaster Training Center [55] (Box F1)
  - Cashier Tabulating, Constance Probst [56] (Box F1)
  - Museums Building Tour-Children [57] (Box F1)
  - Labor Conference, Machinists Institute, Hospital Dietitians [58] (Box F1)
  - Medical Triennial Guides [59 a] (Box F1)
  - Revelli Anniversary January 1960 [59 b-60] (Box F1)
  - Hill Auditorium [62] (Box F1)
  - Computer, West Engineering, Haddad [64] (Box F1)
  - Mental Health Dedication January 1960 [65] (Box F1)
  - Medical Center, Special Publicity [66] (Box F1)
  - Medical Bacteriology Department [67 a] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix Art Museum, Fluids, Interiors [67 b] (Box F1)
  - Revelli Anniversary [67 c] (Box F1)
  - Girls in Air Force ROTC [68] (Box F1)
  - Music School, Class, Klien Girls [69] (Box F1)
  - Medical Center, Color Television January 1960 [70] (Box F1)
  - League, A. Alpert, Mrs. Norris [71] (Box F1)
  - Opera February 29, 1960 [72-73] (Box F1)
  - International Wives [74] (Box F1)
  - Frances Greer, Stanley Quartet [75] (Box F1)
  - Speech, Television [77] (Box F1)
  - International Wives [79] (Box F1)
  - Vidor Painting, International Center [80] (Box F1)
  - Shah, Egyptian ? [81] (Box F1)
  - International Wives [82 a-b] (Box F1)
  - Ice Skater [83] (Box F1)
  - Music School, Crowded Conditions [84] (Box F1)
  - Wives [85] (Box F1)
  - International Wives [86 a] (Box F1)
  - Wives [86 b] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix (Greenhouse) [87 a] (Box F1)
  - International Wives [87 b] (Box F1)
  - Radio Telescope [88-89] (Box F1)
  - Hospital School, Isotope Unit [90] (Box F1)
  - Hospital Dietitians, Planning Group [91] (Box F1)
  - Interlochen Laundromat [92] (Box F1)
  - Lillian Hellman [93] (Box F1)
  - North Campus, Instrument Shop, Psychological Services [94] (Box F1)
  - International Wives [95] (Box F1)
  - Pathology SRC [96] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix, Fire Fighting [96 b] (Box F1)
  - Hospital, British Doctors [97] (Box F1)
  - Michifish (Synchronized Swimming) [98] (Box F1)
  - Wood Technology [99] (Box F1)
  - Law, Smith, Harver [100] (Box F1)
  - Michifish [101] (Box F1)
  - Allan Smith, Yntema, Hatcher [102] (Box F1)
  - Campus Scenes [103] (Box F1)
  - Dean Moore Dinner [104-105] (Box F1)
  - Psychology, Pinball, Mrs. Rowe, Dean Stason [106 a] (Box F1)
  - Industrial Engineering [106b] (Box F1)
  - Campus Scenes [107] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix Train [108] (Box F1)
  - Honors Convocation [109] (Box F1)
  - Burton tower Bell Ringing [110] (Box F1)
  - Journalism, Lindstrom [111] (Box F1)
  - Dr. Fries and Class [112] (Box F1)
  - Land, Arch, Arboretum [113] (Box F1)
  - Survey Research Center [114] (Box F1)
  - Career Women (Life) [115 a] (Box F1)
  - Russian Tour, Hometowns [115 b] (Box F1)
  - Burton Tower, Bells (Zvon Ringing Directed by Percival Price [117 a-c] (Box F1)
  - Alumni, Regis, Hatchers [118] (Box F1)
  - Alumni, Elder Alumni [119 a] (Box F1)
  - Alumni Dinner, Distinguished Service Awards [119 b-121] (Box F1)
  - Commencement [122-127] (Box F1)
  - Fire College [128-129] (Box F1)
  - TV, Business Administration, Rambler Rocket [130] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix Researcher [131] (Box F1)
  - Felheim [132] (Box F1)
  - Journalism, Hometowns [133] (Box F1)
  - Journalism Workshop [134] (Box F1)
  - Band Conductors Conference [135] (Box F1)
  - Fresh Air Camp [136-137] (Box F1)
  - Student Activities Addition [138] (Box F1)
  - Fresh Air Camp [139] (Box F1)
  - Special Publicity [140] (Box F1)
  - Great Lakes [141-147] (Box F1)
  - Belgians [148 a] (Box F1)
  - Welding [148 b] (Box F1)
  - General Library Ceiling Collapse July 1960 [149] (Box F1)
  - Group III, Journalism Hometowns [150] (Box F1)
  - Girls, Baroque Trio [151] (Box F1)
  - Girls State [152-153] (Box F1)
  - Biology Garden, personnel [154] (Box F1)
  - Fred Family, Music, Russian Tour [156] (Box F1)
  - Kresge, School Services [157 a] (Box F1)
  - Spinetta, Psychology, Worms [157 b] (Box F1)
  - Public Health [158] (Box F1)
  - Balloon [159] (Box F1)
  - Dearborn Extension, Offices, Engineering Lab [160] (Box F1)
  - Dearborn, Hometowns [161 a-b] (Box F1)
  - Biological Station [163-164] (Box F1)
  - Public Health [165] (Box F1)
  - WUOM, Phillips-Rappaport [166] (Box F1)
  - Football, Library Rare Book Room [167] (Box F1)
  - Cohen, Computer [168] (Box F1)
  - Fisheries, Baldwin, ELI [171] (Box F1)
  - Architectural Design [172] (Box F1)
  - Dearborn Center [173] (Box F1)
  - Public Health, Law School Library, Seminar [174] (Box F1)
  - Fritz Lehman, Journalism Fellows [175] (Box F1)
  - Glee Club, Trip to Europe [176 a-z] (Box F1)
  - Homecoming Displays, Birds [177] (Box F1)
  - Campus Scenes [178] (Box F1)
  - Special Publicity, Dance [179] (Box F1)
  - Play, Lydia Merd, Dance [180] (Box F1)
  - Special Publicity [181] (Box F1)
  - WUOM, Hospital [182] (Box F1)
  - International Wives [183] (Box F1)
  - Pharmacy [184] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix Cyclotron [185] (Box F1)
  - Record [186] (Box F1)
  - Public Health [187] (Box F1)
  - Golf, Barb Rotirg, Han Seong [188] (Box F1)
  - Student (?) Government [189] (Box F1)
  - Flint College [190] (Box F1)
  - Phoenix, Chemistry [191] (Box F1)
  - Band Practice, Campus Scenes, Vidar Painting [192] (Box F1)
  - Mental Health, Kresge Gift [193] (Box F1)
  - Computer Center [194] (Box F1)
  - Modern Dance, Stason Portrait [195] (Box F1)
  - Alumni Awards, Modern dance, Stason Portrait [196] (Box F1)
  - Mental Health [197] (Box F1)
  - Campus Scenes, Undergraduate Library [198] (Box F1)
  - Law School, Music School (Instruments) [199] (Box F1)
  - Pharmacology Building, Glee Club [201] (Box F1)
  - Hospital, Halloween Costume [202] (Box F1)
  - Naval Tank [203] (Box F1)
  - Marilyn Mason Brown [204] (Box F1)
  - Football Scrimmage [205] (Box F1)
  - Development Council September 24, 1960 [206] (Box F1)
  - Public Health [207] (Box F1)
  - Football [208] (Box F1)
  - Nursing [209] (Box F1)
  - Construction, WUOM, Jerome Hines [210] (Box F1)
  - Band Hometowns [211-215] (Box F1)
  - Flint Executive Committee, Naval Tank, Van Cliburn [216] (Box F1)
  - Band Practice [217] (Box F1)
  - Football Hometowns [218] (Box F1)
  - Football, Oregon [219] (Box F1)
  - Football, Oregon, Development Council [220] (Box F1)
  - Football, Duke October 8, 1960 [221] (Box F1)
  - Football, Band, Crowd scenes [222] (Box F1)
  - Football, Duke October 8, 1960 [223] (Box F1)
  - Football, Band, Duke October 8, 1960 [224] (Box F1)
  - Football, Duke October 8, 1960 [225] (Box F1)
  - Football, Band, Northwestern [226-228] (Box F3)
  - Football, Minnesota October 1960 [229-230] (Box F3)
  - Football, Band, Minnesota [232] (Box F3)
  - Football, Band, Brown Jug, Minnesota October 1960 [233] (Box F3)
  - Football, Minnesota October 1960 [234] (Box F3)
  - Football, Brown Jug, Minnesota October 1960 [235] (Box F3)
  - Football, Wisconsin, Cleland and Rosalie [236] (Box F3)
  - Band Parade, Wisconsin [237] (Box F3)
  - Football, Hotel Parade, Wisconsin [238] (Box F3)
  - Band, Wisconsin Dinner [239] (Box F3)
  - Band Concert, Wisconsin [240] (Box F3)
  - Band Parade, Wisconsin [241] (Box F3)
  - Football, Illinois October 1960 [243-245] (Box F3)
  - Undergraduate Library, Audio Room [249] (Box F3)
  - Student for Pickering, Horace Davey, Church [250] (Box F3)
  - Higher Education, Doctoral Committee [251] (Box F3)
  - Alumni, Museum, Physics, Students for Pickering [252] (Box F3)
  - Hazel Losh [253] (Box F3)
  - Foreign Administrators [254] (Box F3)
  - MHRI, Health Services, West Engineering, Speech-Frieze [255] (Box F3)
  - Pharmacy, Hospital-Test Kitchen, Eye Machine [256] (Box F3)
  - Special Publicity [257] (Box F3)
  - Youth Symphony December 1960 [258] (Box F3)
  - Rosseels, Williams Papers [259] (Box F3)
  - Pharmacology [260] (Box F3)
  - Girl, Marine ROTC [261] (Box F3)
  - Math, Hospital Admittance, Psychology [262] (Box F3)
  - Education Conference, Larkin, Law School [263] (Box F3)
  - Cyclotron Inspection, Kish, Dentistry [264] (Box F3)
  - Kismet [265-266] (Box F3)
  - English Language Institute [267] (Box F3)
  - South Quad [268] (Box F3)
  - Music Conference [269] (Box F3)
  - Speech [270-271] (Box F3)
  - Speech-Nursery [272] (Box F3)
  - Balloons [273-274] (Box F3)
  - Special Publicity [275] (Box F3)
  - Architectural Design, Professor Heller [276 a] (Box F3)
  - Commencement [276 b-c] (Box F3)
  - Business Administration [277] (Box F3)
  - Phoenix Dinner, Dr. Glaser, Ford Scholars [278-279] (Box F3)
  - Public Health, Dr. Francis Lab [281 a-b] (Box F3)
  - Devlin, Wallenback, Sekker [282] (Box F3)
  - Rodent Research, Engineering [283] (Box F3)
  - Pharmacy, Education Conference [284] (Box F3)
  - Anatomy [285-288] (Box F3)
  - Symphony Band [289-293] (Box F3)
  - Navy ROTC [294] (Box F3)
  - Baroque Trio [295] (Box F3)
  - Health Service Safety measures, Children and Poison [296-298] (Box F3)
  - Teacher Education Conference [299] (Box F3)
  - Pharmacy [300] (Box F3)
  - Michigan Week, Cyclotron Construction [301] (Box F3)
  - Church Construction, Michigan Week [302] (Box F3)
  - Public Health, Histology [303] (Box F3)
  - Law [304-305] (Box F3)
  - May Festival Group, Athletics, Law School [306] (Box F3)
  - Governor Swainson, Fluid Dynamics Lab [307-308] (Box F3)
  - Medical Center program [311] (Box F3)
  - Party [313] (Box F3)
  - Hospital Dietetics [314-315] (Box F3)
  - Prosthetics Shop, Steigerwall, Insurance Analysis, Miller [316] (Box F3)
  - Law School, Lincoln Letters [317] (Box F3)
  - Extension Service [318] (Box F3)
  - Kindergarten [319] (Box F3)
  - University of Michigan Birthday Party, Statler, Detroit [320] (Box F3)
  - Law School Practice Court, Cyclotron Construction [321] (Box F3)
  - Pierpont [322] (Box F3)
  - Law School Fire Damage [323] (Box F3)
  - Psychology Class, McConnell, Angell Hall [324] (Box F3)
  - Housing [325-327] (Box F3)
  - Professor Randall [328] (Box F3)
  - Chemistry [329] (Box F3)
  - West Engineering Roof [330] (Box F3)
  - Magnets, Fluid Dynamics Lab [331] (Box F3)
  - Professor Chambers [332] (Box F4)
  - Bacteriology Department, Vera Collars [333] (Box F4)
  - Phoenix Reactor, ICA Grantees [334] (Box F4)
  - Architecture and Design Emil Weddige [335] (Box F4)
  - Burton Tower Offices [336] (Box F4)
  - Harris Hall, Interiors and Exteriors [337] (Box F4)
  - Alumni Dinner June 1955 [338] (Box F4)
  - Journalism July, 1956 [339] (Box F4)
  - Commencement June 1955 [340] (Box F4)
  - ELI Language Lab [341] (Box F4)
  - Polio-Salk Vaccine [342] (Box F4)
  - Architecture and Design Classroom [343] (Box F4)
  - Biological Station [344] (Box F4)
  - Speech Camp [345] (Box F4)
  - Interlochen [346] (Box F4)
  - Fresh Air Camp [347 a] (Box F4)
  - Michifish [347 b] (Box F4)
  - Engineering, Grenade Testing [349] (Box F4)
  - Golf [350] (Box F4)
  - Pharmacy, Rheometer [351] (Box F4)
  - Hospital School Animals [352] (Box F4)
  - Special Publicity [353] (Box F4)
  - Spring Weekend, Glee Club [354] (Box F4)
  - Summer Session, Special Publicity [355] (Box F4)
  - Speech Clinic [356-357] (Box F4)
  - May Festival [358] (Box F4)
  - May Festival, Philharmonic Orchestra and Sigma Chi [359] (Box F4)
  - C.E. Bentley [360] (Box F4)
  - May Festival Rehearsal [361] (Box F4)
  - Radio Telescope, Soviet Visitors [362] (Box F4)
  - Honors Convocation, Hill Auditorium [363] (Box F4)
  - Dinner, Spring Weekend, Safety Bill [364] (Box F4)
  - International Center Tea [365] (Box F4)
  - SRC, Max Littlejohn [366 a-b] (Box F4)
  - Naval Tank, NA-ME, Pediatrics [367] (Box F4)
  - Hatchers [368] (Box F4)
  - Stanley Quartet, Revelli Lantern [369] (Box F4)
  - Symphony Band, Legislative Resolution [370] (Box F4)
  - Michigan League, Presentation of Husser Portrait [371] (Box F4)
  - Symphony Band, Diag Concert [372] (Box F4)
  - Commencement, fathers-sons [373] (Box F4)
  - News Service Office [374] (Box F4)
  - Hospital Front Doors, Administrative Meeting [375] (Box F4)
  - Naval tank, Woodman Award, ELT Record Presentation [376] (Box F4)
  - Commencement Engineering Reunion [377] (Box F4)
  - Commencement, Stadium [378-382] (Box F4)
  - Commencement, Alumni Luncheon, Alumni Awards [383-385] (Box F4)
  - Commencement, Alumnae Council I [386-387] (Box F4)
  - Continental (?) Composers Conference, Office [388] (Box F4)
  - Hospital, Heart Patient, Great Lakes Fisheries Group [389] (Box F4)
  - Registration Card, Jan Teig, M. Waterman, Business Administration [390] (Box F4)
  - Women's Golf Tournament [391-392 a] (Box F4)
  - NSF Plastic Tube Failures [392 b-c] (Box F4)
  - Tom Gable Port at Desk [392 d] (Box F4)
  - NSF, Environmental Health Congress [392 e-401] (Box F4)
  - Symphony Band Tour [500-550] (Box F4)
  - Peace Corp [no number] (Box F4)
- Series G 1949-1970 (Mainly Aerial Negatives)
  SERIES G (2.5 linear ft.; 1949-1970)consists of aerial survey photographs; Mainly 7" x 7" negatives and contact prints of an aerial survey of the Ann Arbor area from 1965 to 1967. Material in Boxes G-2 and G-3 was accessioned in 1997 and consists of 5" x 7" negatives (including some color negatives) and some contact prints of aerial views from 1949 to 1970. Negatives are arranged by the numbering system used by News and Information Services. Images are primarily of the University of Michigan but also include aerial views of businesses in and around Ann Arbor, as well as views of, and businesses in surrounding communities. Some non-aerial views are included such as a series of negatives of Ann Arbor churches dating from approximately 1959.
  A brief index to Series G is included in the inventory section of this finding aid. Subject access, however, is best achieved by reviewing descriptions on envelopes housing the material, and for part, by using the index cards located in the reading room.
  - A2000-A2016 A5000 (with contact prints) (Box G1)
  - Identified Aerial Negatives, A-Z (also contact prints)
    - Ann Arbor form the South East (Box G1)
    - Ann Arbor Hills Subdivision (Box G1)
    - Bolgus, Georgetown, North Campus, 3 envelopes (Box G1)
    - Central Campus, 2 envelopes (Box G1)
    - Downtown Ann Arbor, 2 envelopes (Box G1)
    - Hospital Area from Northwest 1965 (Box G1)
    - Hospital Area 1966 (Box G1)
    - Huron Towers, Veterans Administration Hospital (Box G1)
    - K-mart (Maple Avenue) (Box G1)
    - Medical Center 1966 (Box G1)
    - New Access-North Campus and Plymouth Road 1965 (Box G1)
    - North Campus, 2 envelopes (Box G1)
    - Packard Street and Ferry Field (Box G1)
    - Palmer Field, Dormitories, and Arboretum (Box G1)
    - Saline (Box G1)
    - University of Michigan Central Campus 1966, 2 envelopes (Box G1)
    - Ypsilanti Ford Plant (Box G1)
  - Unidentified Aerials (largely Ann Arbor and University of Michigan), 100 negatives approximate; with contact prints (Box G1)
  - Identified Aerial Negatives (without contact prints) 1965-1966
    - Ann Arbor Water Station, Spring Street 1965 (Box G1)
    - Boys Training School at Whitmore Lake 1965 (Box G1)
    - Brighton 1965 (Box G1)
    - Campus 1965, 2 envelopes (Box G1)
    - Campus Aerial 1966 (Box G1)
    - Cedar Bend (Baits Housing) Construction North Campus 1965 (Box G1)
    - Chelsea 1965 (Box G1)
    - Community College Site 1965 (Box G1)
    - Concordia College 1965 (Box G1)
    - County Estates (Student Trailers) 1965 (Box G1)
    - Dearborn Campus 1966 (Box G1)
    - Department of Commercial Fisheries 1966 (Box G1)
    - Dexter 1965 (Box G1)
    - East on M-14 to US 23 (Box G1)
    - Eastern Michigan University 1965 (Box G1)
    - Greek Theater Site, Ypsilanti 1965 (Box G1)
    - Hamburg (Looking North) 1965 (Box G1)
    - Huron River Building Site (Near Dexter) 1965 (Box G1)
    - I-94 Overpass at Ypsilanti 1965 (Box G1)
    - Industrial Building (West on Jackson & I 94) 1965 (Box G1)
    - Interchange, US 23 and I 96 1965 (Box G1)
    - Manchester 1965 (Box G1)
    - Mary Markley and School of Public Health (Box G1)
    - Michigan Seamless Tube Co. South Lyon 1965 (Box G1)
    - Milan 1965 (Box G1)
    - North Campus Cedar Bend Apartments (Baits) 1965 (Box G1)
    - North Campus Commons 1965 (Box G1)
    - North Campus Housing 1965 (Box G1)
    - North Campus Northeast View 1965 (Box G1)
    - Park-Hudson Mills 1965 (Box G1)
    - Parke Davis and Bendix (Box G1)
    - Peach Mountain 1965 (Box G1)
    - Pinckney 1965 (Box G1)
    - Pinckney Recreation Area State Park 1965 (Box G1)
    - Salem 1965 (Box G1)
    - Site of Fatal Accident, Dr. Huelke (Box G1)
    - Stadium Looking South 1965 (Box G1)
    - State Park Half Moon Lake 1965 (Box G1)
    - Traver Valley Apartments, Ann Arbor 1965 (Box G1)
    - University of Michigan Incinerator, North Campus 1965 (Box G1)
    - Whitmore Lake (Box G1)
  - 9" x 9" Aerial Negatives With Contact Prints (Box G1)
  - Contact Prints with no Accompanying Negatives (Box G1)
  - Negative Reels of Aerial Survey, Urban and Rural Washtenaw County (?) including some U-M campus, 3 reels (Box G1)
  - "A" Series (5" x 7" aerial views) 1957-1964
    - A-1-A-96 (with gaps in sequence) (Box G2)
  - "a" Series (5" x 7" aerial views) 1953-1960
    - a-1-a-77 (with gaps in sequence) (Box G2)
  - "AERO" Series (5" x 7" aerial views with some contact prints)
    - AERO 4, Ford Plant, Ypsilanti 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 5, Ford Plant, Ypsilanti 1952 (Box G3)
    - AERO 31, Ann Arbor High (Pioneer) Site 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 32, Slauson School Construction 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 37, Michigan Seamless Tube Company, South Lyon 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 41, Ford Plant, Ypsilanti 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 56, Slauson School Construction 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 62, Swischer's Subdivision circa 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 76, Ann Arbor High School (Pioneer) Site 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 77, Court House 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 9, St. Joseph's Hospital Construction 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 80, Ann Arbor High School (Pioneer) Site 1954 (Box G3)
    - AERO 87-88, St. Joseph's Hospital Construction 1954 (Box G3)
  - "CA" Series (5" x 7" color aerials) 1960-1967
    - CA-1, Stadium October 1960 (Box G3)
    - CA-3, Flint Campus October 1960 (Box G3)
    - CA-4, Dearborn Center October 1960 (Box G3)
    - CA-5, Dearborn Veteran's Hospital October 1960 (Box G3)
    - CA-6, Metropolitan Airport October 1960 (Box G3)
    - CA-7, (labeled Law School, actually Stadium with Crisler construction) (Box G3)
    - CA-7, Interlochen (multiple negatives) June 1961 (Box G3)
    - CA-8, Medical Center 1960 (Box G3)
    - CA-8, Stadium, Football Team on Field October 1961 (Box G3)
    - CA-9, Central Campus "good shot taken from over NC," 1967 (Box G3)
    - CA-10, Eastern Michigan University "good shot from east," 1967 (Box G3)
    - CA 10, Central Campus Aerial 1964 (Box G3)
    - CA-11, Stadium (full and empty) 1964 (Box G3)
    - CA-12, Ferry Field 1964 (Box G3)
  - 5 x 7 Series (Buildings and Churches (Non-aerial), by John Alley)
    - 5 x 7-1, Student Activities Building circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-2, Lane Hall circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-3, St. Mary's Student Chapel circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-4, Lutheran Student Center and Chapel circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-5, University Lutheran Chapel and Student Center circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-6, First Methodist Church circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-7, First Presbyterian Church circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-8, First Unitarian Church circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-9, Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-10, American Baptist Student Fellowship Building circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-11, Christian Reformed Campus Chapel circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-12, Grace Bible Church circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-13, B'Nai B'rith Hillel Foundation circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-14, First Congregational Church circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-15, Guild House circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-16, St. Nicholas Church (altar only) circa 1959 (Box G3)
    - 5 x 7-17, Episcopal Student Foundation Chapel Interior circa 1959 (Box G3)
  - Miscellaneous 5" x 7" Aerial Negatives
    - Ann Arbor Airport 1959 (Box G3)
    - Ann Arbor Water Works, Sunset Road 1951, 2 envelopes (Box G3)
    - Barton Hills House 1949 (Box G3)
    - Barton Pumping Station 1951 (Box G3)
    - Bass Lake 1950 (Box G3)
    - Botanical Gardens undated, 3 folders (Box G3)
    - Campus Area
      - 1969 (Box G3)
      - 1970, 3 envelopes (Box G3)
      - Undated, 4 envelopes (Box G3)